Guide to the Office of University Special Events records, 1981-2011 RG0111
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- 175th anniversary celebration materials, 1996; RG0111 Series 12; 28 Linear feet (Box 19, Box 4, Box 1, Box 3, Box 2)
  - Letter From Washington and Jefferson College PA, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Letter From University of Washington, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Letter From Washington State University, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Letter From Western Washington University, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Letter From Washington High School Indiana, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Letter From George Washington High School, San Francisco, CA, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Letter From George Washington High School, L.A., CA, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Letter From George Washington High School, Denver, CO, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Letter From Washington High School, Georgia, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Letter From Washington High School, Indiana, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Letter From Washington High School, Iowa, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Letter From Washington Waldorf High School, Maryland, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Letter From Washington Ville High School, New York, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Letter From Washington, Georgia, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Letter From Washington Senior High School, Ohio, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Kentland, Indiana, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Letter From Washington, Indiana, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Letter From Washington, Iowa, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Letter From Washington, Mass., undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Letter From Washington, Mississippi, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Letter From Washington, Nebraska, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Bergen County, New Jersey, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Long Valley, New Jersey, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Centreville, Ohio, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Coldwater, Ohio, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Apollo, PA, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Barto, PA, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Shoylkill, PA, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Letter From Washington Township, Tunkhannack, PA, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Letter From Washington, Texas, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Letter From Town of Washington, Eau Claire, Wisconsin, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Package of Marketing Class Proposals for GW 175 Anniversary, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Lead Strikes Of The Presidential Medallion, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - GW Paperweight, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Folder Of Opening Convocation Proclamations, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Folder Of Charter Day Proclamations, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Panorama photos of 1996 commencement on the Ellipse, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    2 photos
  - Binder - 175th Anniversary Celebration Master Archival Volume, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Academic Programs, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Academic Programs Letters To Recipients (175th), undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Academic Programs Proposals (175th), undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Academic Programs Proposals (175th), undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Academic Programs Proposals (175th), undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 175th Academic Programs Revest For Proposals, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Marshall Alcorn and Judy Plotz Conference On Psychoanalysis And Post colonialism, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Joseph Cordes Challenges To Economic Policy In The Year 2002 Beyond, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Shana Epstein - The Public Service Academy, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ben Fritz - The Music Of GWU, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Joseph Giordano - GWU Medical Center, Transforming Medical Education With Virtue Reality, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Good Enough And Hoffman "Technology And Health Can Issues And Opportunities (175th)", undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Lois Graf - Women In The Work Place, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Griffith - "Social Justice and The Welfare State" and "Liberalism And Its Critics", undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Guenther - Music Commission, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - E. P. Harper - George Gamow Symposium, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Greg Kearsley - A Celebration At Teaching Excellence, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Diana Lipscomb - Our Biodiversity Legacy - A Dialog Between Policy Makers and Systematic Scientists, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Steven Livingston - Current Trends In Political Communication Research, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Marie Maralit - Addressing The Challenge Of An Aging Population In The 21st Century - A University's Response To The White House Conference On Aging, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - C. Dianne Martin - Visualizing Amazonia: A State Of The Art Multimedia And Graphics Learning Center At The NZP, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Sally Moaty - Forum In Developmental Genetics And Disease, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Honey Nashman And Peter Konwersk; Symposium On Social Change, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Jane Neapolitan: Mentors Make A Difference, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Catherine Pickar: Choral Composition And Performance, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Jeffrey Rosenstein - Symposium On Neuroscience And Behavior, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Frederic Siegel - Societal Needs And The Environment, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Sieglman Symposium On The '96 Presidential Campaign, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Robert Smythe (175th) Conference In Memory Of Protestor Solomon Kullback, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Nahid Khoziemeh - Engineering Towards The 21st Century, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Creative and Performing Arts Committee (175th), undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Executive Committee (175th), undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Public Relations Committee, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Special Events Committee, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Special Events: 175th Anniversary Kick Off, 11/18/1992 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Student Initiatives Committee (175th), undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Student Initiatives: Class of '96 Gift (175th), undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - 175th Anniversary Reports and Lists, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Symposium For Social Change, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: The Challenge Of An Aging Population, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Women In The Workplace, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Technology and Healthcare, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: George Gamow Symposium, 04/12/1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Psychoanalysis And Post Colonial Conference, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Symposium On The 1996 Presidential Election, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Media Election In The Next Millennium, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Mentors Make A Difference, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Kullback Memorial Research Conference, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Graduate School Fellowships, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 175th Anniversary Academic Programs: Colonnade Gallery Exhibits, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 175th Anniversary Dimock Gallery: George Washington Still B Moc, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 175th Anniversary Dimock Gallery: The Boston Boys And General Gage, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 175th Anniversary Dimock Gallery: Washington Photogaphy, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 175th Anniversary Dimock Gallery: Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 175th Anniversary Lisner Auditorium Series, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 175th Anniversary Dimock Gallery: George Washington Still B Moc, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 175th Anniversary Music Dept: Completely George Concert, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 175th Anniversary Music Dept: Para Bolae Salomonis, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 175th Anniversary Music Dept: Steiner Benefit Concert, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 175th Anniversary Safer Sculpture Donation: "Limits Of Infinity III", undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 175th Anniversary D. C. Phone Book Cover, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - 175th Anniversary Graphics Standard Manuals, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - 175th Anniversary From Strength To Strength Announcements, Ads, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - 175th Anniversary From Strength To Strength Sales and Order Forms, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - 175th Anniversary From Strength To Strength Distribution, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - 175th Anniversary 175th Anniversary Paper Series, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - 175th Anniversary Graphic, Cards and Invitation, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - 175th Anniversary Graphics Other Departments Anniversary Looks, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - 175th Anniversary Graphics Anniversary Graphics Anniversary Letterheads, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - 175th Anniversary General Articles Regarding The Anniversary, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - 175th Anniversary Buy George Catalog Of Merchandise, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - 175th Anniversary Commemorative Pepsi Cans, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - 175th Anniversary 175th Flags Around The World, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - 175th Anniversary Commemorative Posta Plate, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - 175th Anniversary Miscellaneous Articles, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Anniversary WWII posters, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Copies of images from history book, 1996; Series 12 (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
  - 175th anniversary executive committee binder, Jon Tarnow, 1992-1996; Series 12 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- 175th anniversary electronic time capsule, 1996; RG0111 Series 13; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  This is a collection of two copies of The George Washington University's 175th anniversary electronic time capsules. This includes compact discs and a printed questionnaire used for 1,900 students and staff responses about their lives and The George Washington University. The material is from 1996 and will be opened in 2021.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Some student material is restricted - check with archives staff for more information.
- Sweat shirt, 1995; RG0111 Series 14; 1 Linear feet (Box 1)
  It is a copy of the sweat shirt given to Bill Cosby to wear during his November 1995 performance.
  - 175th anniversary sweat shirt, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    This is a copy of the sweat shirt given to Bill Cosby to wear during his November 1995 performance. This sweat shirt commemorates the 175th anniversary of the University. Formerly Acc# 701.
- Memorabilia, 1995-2000; RG0111 Series 15; 1 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains t-shirts, sweat-shirts, and other The George Washington University memorabilia, such as aprons, paperweights, and 3-D glasses. They range in date from 1995 to 2000 and celebrate different university events.
- 175th anniversary banner, 1996; RG0111 Series 16; 4 Linear feet (Object 1)
  This series includes a banner from the 175th anniversary celebration of the university in 1996.
- 175th anniversary unused posters, 1996; RG0111 Series 18; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains six unused poster ideas for 175th anniversary. They are from 1996.
- Office files, 1993-2005; RG0111 Series 19; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains invitations, flyers, stationary, bookmark, stickers, minutes, business card, drafts, postcards, correspondence, questionnaire, calendar of events, speeches, ticket, and programs. They range in date from 1993 to 2005. They concern Presidential Inaugural Balls, holiday parties, the 175th anniversary of The George Washington University, charter day, committees, George Washington's birthday celebration, and other special events.
  - George Washington's Birthday Celebration, 1996-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - History of GW - 175th Anniversary, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - History of GW - 175th Anniversary Charter Day, 02/09/1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - History of GW - 175th Anniversary Committees, 01/06/1993 --10/06/1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Special Events, 01/20/1997 --01/20/2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)